<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>home on mkix0x</title>
    <link>https://mkix0x.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in home on mkix0x</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="https://mkix0x.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Devlog</title>
      <link>https://mkix0x.com/devlog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 21:15:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mkix0x.com/devlog/</guid>
      <description>2023.02.20 Today I started a new project - the same game I&amp;rsquo;ve been working on for a while.
Perhaps unconsciously, I believed that starting a fresh project would inspire some motivation and optimism. However, I have fallen into the same trap. I found myself once again fine-tuning basic actions instead of focusing on the bigger picture.
It&amp;rsquo;s easy to get caught up in the thrill of quick bursts of dopamine from making minor improvements, but this doesn&amp;rsquo;t bring me any closer to actually releasing the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roadmap</title>
      <link>https://mkix0x.com/roadmap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2023 13:34:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mkix0x.com/roadmap/</guid>
      <description>Upcoming 0.1.1 Improvements to the core actions of the game.
Movement
[DONE] Implement bounce sound and visual effects to improve visibility of the walking state. [SKIPPED] (Add dust effects to enhance the feeling of movement.) [SKIPPED] (Add haptic feedback to provide a tactile sensation when moving.) Skipped some of the feedback since it was too much for an action that happens that often.
Throw
Add trail effect for the axe to follow, making it easier for players to track its trajectory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Finishing</title>
      <link>https://mkix0x.com/finishing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 02:30:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mkix0x.com/finishing/</guid>
      <description>You need confidence and a proven track record to finish games constantly. Start with small projects to build your skills.
Outline your game down into achievable high-level milestones to decrease the mental load and stay on track. Keep it flexible.
Prioritize important outcomes for each milestone and focus on progress, rather than details.
Striving for perfection can hinder your progress. Aim for &amp;ldquo;good enough&amp;rdquo; results instead.
Improve your finishing skills and perseverance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Risk</title>
      <link>https://mkix0x.com/risk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 12:44:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mkix0x.com/risk/</guid>
      <description>Masahiro Sakurai published a video where he mentioned that rewards should be the first thing you consider. However, this videos lacks cruicial information.
Yes, you should consider rewards, but to do that you need to know what your risks are. It&amp;rsquo;s possible that you don&amp;rsquo;t have awareness what rewards truly are. Put simply, rewards exist to mitigate risks. If a reward doesn&amp;rsquo;t reduce a risk, then it&amp;rsquo;s not a reward.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
